# **JUSTIN BECKER**

Twin Lake, MI 49457 • linkedin.com/in/justin-becker-dev

## Junior Software Developer (RPG)

I'm a dedicated professional with a diverse skillset and over a decade of experience in patient, student, and customer-facing roles. I'm seeking to utilize my programming knowledge and creativity as a junior developer on the IBMi platform. I thrive on learning new technologies and skills, with a particular interest in the modernization of IBMi/iSeries/AS400 software.

#### Skill Highlights:

- RPG ILE/Free Form/SQLRPGLE
- **Access Client Solutions**
- Rational Developer for i
- Java Development
- C# Development
- SQL Server, MySQL
- JavaScript, PHP, CSS, HTML
- Agile/Scrum/Waterfall SDLC
- **Detailed Documentation**

### Experience

Junior Programmer Analyst – 2024 to Present Developer Intern – 2024 to 2024 Session Musician / Audio Engineer – 2021 to 2024 Cardiac Telemetry Specialist – 2020 to 2021 Level III Pharmacy Tech / Liaison – 2018 to 2020 Pharmacy Technician – 2016 to 2018 **College Tutor / Administrative Aid –** 2012 – 2016

#### Junior Programmer Analyst | Innovative Software Solutions inc. | Remote

- Developed RPGLE maintenance programs for legacy IBMi-based software.
- Web/mobile development and API integration.
- Continuing education in new languages and frameworks.

#### Intern | CDR Software | Remote

- Provided technical support for iSeries-based software suite designed for managing distribution operations.
- Identified deficiencies in documentation and worked with technical writers to resolve them.
- Used critical thinking and investigation skills to identify solutions to customer issues which lacked sufficient documentation.

#### Session Musician / Audio Engineer | Freelance | Remote

- Developed and sustained a client base through strategic marketing on digital platforms and leveraging personal networks.
- Engaged in collaborative projects with producers, composers, and fellow musicians to create original songs and arrangements.
- Specialized in bespoke composition, delivering tailor-made songs to meet diverse client specifications.
- Offered comprehensive audio engineering services, encompassing mixing, mastering, audio editing, and sound design, utilizing professional equipment and software.

#### Cardiac Telemetry Technician | Trinity Health Hospital | Muskegon, MI

- Served as a vital member of a healthcare team which consisted of over 20 professionals and specialists.
- Interpreted and documented patient heart rhythms, including dysrhythmias, using ECG technology and specialized software.
- Alerted resuscitation teams to assist patients experiencing life -threatening dysrhythmias or critical changes in vital signs.
- Sanitized medical equipment in accordance with hospital infection control procedures.

#### Level III Pharmacy Technician | Trinity Health Pharmacy | Muskegon, MI

- Coordinated with teams of over 25 professionals consisting of physicians, pharmacists, and RN case managers to determine optimal medication regimen for each unique patient circumstance.
- Conducted formulary queries and adjudication with insurance companies to ensure financial sustainability for patient medication therapies.
- Educated patients and caregivers on medication usage, side effects, and interactions.

#### Pharmacy Technician | Trinity Health Pharmacy / Meijer Pharmacy | Muskegon, MI

- Ordered, received, and shelved pharmacy inventory.
- Transcribed prescriptions given over the phone by medical practitioners.
- Conducted point-of-sale transactions and reconciliation.

#### College Tutor / Administrative Aid | Muskegon Community College | Muskegon, MI

- Provided administrative support to faculty in the College Success Center.
- Tutored college students in subjects such as statistics, math, and English composition.
- Responsible for proctoring student exams.

### **Achievements**

 $1^{\text{st}}$  place winner of WMCPA's iCON2024 student RPG programming competition | Muskegon Community College

Advanced to Pharmacy Liaison within 3 years, pioneering a new role in the organization which increased Meds to Go program utilization by over 50% | Trinity Health Pharmacy

Trained as an Epic Systems super user and assisted in facilitating nationwide EMR transition | Trinity Health Pharmacy

Selected for a position as a Student Liaison on the COMMON Education Foundation board where my input was used to shape student outreach strategies.

Recipient of Muskegon Community College's 2024 Award for Excellence in Software Development. | Muskegon Community College

Developed and implemented an orientation program for new technicians to ensure consistency in processes, which promoted both efficiency and patient safety | Trinity Health Pharmacy

## **Education**

Muskegon Community College • Software development with a focus on RPG | Education | Nursing

**COMMON • Associate Application Developer Certification** 

Muskegon Community College • Midrange Programming Certification

Meijer Pharmacy Technician Training Program • Pharmacy Technician License

# **Technology Summary**

Languages RPG ILE/RPG IV, SQL, DDS, CL, HTML5, JavaScript, PHP, CSS, Java, C, C++, C#

**Development Tools** Eclipse Rational Developer (RDI), Visual Studio, VSCode, phpMyAdmin, SQL

Server Management Studio, Android Studio, JavaFX Scene Builder, Unity, Reaper,

**FL Studio** 

**Supporting Tools** Microsoft Suite, Access Client Solutions, Atlassian JIRA, Autotask, WordPress,

GitHub